

Systems Analyst

Email: steveriven94@gmail.com Address: Choi Hung Phone: 97100819

OBJECTIVE

Experienced Full-stack engineer with a Bachelors degree in Computer Science and familiarity with several programming languages, such as React, Node.Js, Looking forward to demonstrating my proven abilities in optimizing web functionalities in a challenging and motivating work environment.

EXPERIENCE

Jun 2022 - Present

System Analyst

AIA International Limited

- · Mapped and documented interfaces between legacy and newer systems
- Collaborated with developers, testers, and end users to ensure technical compatibility.
- Worked with and developed applications with JAVA, Spring, Spring Boot, and MongoDB as well as worked in troubleshooting methods and documented solutions
- Worked with a team of expert coders to write maintainable code and maintain existing software to improve performance and fix bugs

Mar 2022 - Jun 2022

Senior Engineer, Full Stack Engineer

WeLend

- Build an online e-shop platform by using Next.js for end-user with a lending payments system by using Ruby and Go.
- Pitched ideas on how to improve performance and efficiency.
- Build an online lending registration system for customers to create their lending profile by using Next.js and Go.
- Support the daily business operation with core lending system by Ruby on Rails
- · Using Graphql and React to make user friendly.

Mar 2021 - Mar 2022

Engineer, Full Stack Engineer

WeLend

- Built modern loan platform applications using Next.js, Go, MongoDB, and Ruby on Rails and supported the company's development and testing processes
- Developed effective microservices and web services and created a series of unit tests to ensure that the projects passed all quality benchmarks

Engineer

South China Morning Post

- Web application platform enhancement to improve the performance of speed by using Vue.js
- Create Google optimize A/B test for webpage innovation to attach more audience
- Develop an API for the audience to bookmark and save their favourite article by using python, Express.js and Graphql
- · Developed full featured Auth system by using React and graphql

May 2018 - Nov 2018

Web Programer

WeMine Ltd

- WeChat and Facebook Messenger Integration to build up the business by using PHP
- Developed a fast CMS by using React and PHP Laravel for business user manage their customer

Sep 2016 - Apr 2018

BackEnd Web Engineer

Prospera International Technology

- Developed a CMS by using PHP Laravel to support the business
- Developed a featured stock exchange webpage for South East Asia by using Sails.js

EDUCATION

2014 - 2016

Bachelor of Science (Honours) Scheme in Applied Sciences (Information Systems and Web Technologies)

The Hong Kong Polytechnic University School of Professional Education and Executive Development

SKILLS

- Node.js
- · Vue.js
- · React.js
- HTML
- CSS

LANGUAGES

Cantonese

Native

English

fluent

Mandarin

Advanced